Guide to the School of Architecture, Yale University, Records Concerning Events and Exhibitions
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Student response papers on the symposium "Eero Saarinen: Form Giver of the American Century", 2005; Accession 2005-A-170
  No inventory available.
- Posters, programs and brochures, 2005; Accession 2005-A-192
  - Posters, programs and brochures, 2005 (Box 1)
- Digital images from the "Archeworks" exhibition [computer files], 2001; Accession 2006-A-079 (Box 1)
  - Digital images from the "Archeworks" exhibition, 2001; 4
- Digital images of the exhibition, "Jean Prouve: A Tropical House" [computer files], 2005; Accession 2006-A-080 (Box 1)
  - Digital images of the exhibition, "Jean Prouve: A Tropical House,", 2005; 34 computer files (TIFF)
- Digital images of "3D City: Studies in Density," recent work from MVRDV [computer files], 2002; Accession 2006-A-082 (Box 1)
  - Digital images of "3D City: Studies in Density," recent work from MVRDV, 2002; 23 computer files (TIFF)
- Digital images from the exhibition "Yale-Japan: Revealing New Ground" [computer files], 2002; Accession 2006-A-083 (Box 1)
  - Digital images from the exhibition "Yale-Japan: Revealing New Ground,", 2002; 16
- Digital images of "Arverne" exhibition [computer files], 2002; Accession 2006-A-084
  - Digital images of "Arverne" exhibition, 2002; 2006-A-084-0001; 1 (Box 1)
- Digital images of the exhibit "Ant Farm 1968-1978", 2005; Accession 2006-A-132 (Box 1)
  - Digital images of the exhibit "Ant Farm 1968-1978,", 2005; 21 computer files (TIFF)
- Transparencies of the exhibit "Jean Prouve: A Tropical House" Yale University School of Architecture, 2005; Accession 2006-A-133
  - Transparencies of the exhibit "Jean Prouve: A Tropical House" Yale University School of Architecture, 2005 (Box 1)
- Disclose: 2005-2006 Year-End Exhibit of Student Work, 2006 May 19 - August 4
  - Advanced Graduate Section
    - Ashton Allan; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Eron Ashley; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Seher Aziz; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Scott Baltimore; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Benay Betts; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Katherine Burke; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Namil Byun; Master of Architecture II, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Joyce Chang; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Sung Ik Cho; Master of Architecture II, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Daniel Chung; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Abigail Coover; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Mario Cruzate; Master of Architecture II, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Naomi Darling; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Mark Davis; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Marina Dayton; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - George de Brigard; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Melanie Domino; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Jennifer DuHamel; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Brent Fleming; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Aaron Fox; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Nicholas Friend; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Roy Griffith; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Michael Grogan; Master of Architecture II, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Andrei Harwell; Master of Architecture II, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Drake Hawthorne; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Brian Hopkins; Master of Architecture II, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Nathan Hume; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Sean Khorsandi; Master of Architecture II, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Laura Killam; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Heather Kilmer; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Timothy Kirkby; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Christopher Kitterman; Master of Architecture II, computer file (PDF), 2006
    - Joy Knoblauch; Master of Environmental Design, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Marisa Kurtzman; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Nicole Lambrou; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Allan William Martin; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Julia McCarthy; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Mayur Mehta; Master of Architecture II, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - David Nam; Master of Architecture II, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Frank Nan; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Susan Parapetti; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Emily Younha Rhee; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Christopher Rountos; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Frida Rosenberg; Master of Environmental Design, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Leslie Ryan; Master of Environmental Design, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Frederick Scharmen; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Gray Shealy; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Meaghan Smialowski; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Ross Smith; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Dawn Sowby; Master of Architecture I, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Maxwell Worrell; Master of Architecture II, 2006; computer file (PDF)
  - H.I. Feldman Prize Section, 2006
    - Melanie Domino, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Aaron Fox, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Andrei Harwell + Chris Beardsley, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Jennifer Duhamel, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Laura Killam, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Kitterman + Worrell, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Marisa Kurtzman, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Susan Parapetti, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Fred Scharmen, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - Jeremiah Joseph + Mustapha Jundi, 2006; computer file (PDF)
  - 1st& 2ndYear Student Work Section, 2006
    - 502b Turner Brooks, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - 502b Amy Lelyveld, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - 502b Alan Organschi, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - 502b Hilary Sample, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - 503a Martin Finio, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - 503a Keith Krumwiede, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - 502b Peter de Bretteville, 2006; computer file (PDF)
    - 502b Mario Gooden, 2006; computer file (PDF)
- Images of the exhibition "Ant Farm 1968-1978", 2005; Accession 2006-A-169
  - Images of the exhibition "Ant Farm 1968-1978,", 2005 (Box 1)
- Images of the exhibition "Transcending Type", 2005; Accession 2006-A-170
  - Color transparencies (4x5") of the exhibition "Transcending Type,", 2005 (Box 1)
  - Digital images of the exhibition "Transcending Type,", 2005; 12 computer files (TIFF), 44 computer files (NEF), 27 computer files (JPEG) (Box 2–3)
- Digital images of the exhibition "Rome Project" [computer files], 2005; Accession 2006-A-171
  Taken by Alec Purves, Sophia Gruzdys, Stephen Harby, August 29 to October 28, 2005.
  - Digital images of the exhibition "Rome Project" created by Alec Purves, Sophia Gruzdys, and Stephen Harby, 2005; 28 computer files (TIFF)
- Article, "Pret a Prouve," and Yale Architecture School Film Society poster, 2006; Accession 2006-A-181
  - "Pret a Prouve", 2006 (Box 1)
  - Yale Architecture School Film Society Poster, 2006 Spring (Folder 2)
- Digital images of exhibitions [computer files], 2005; Accession 2006-A-193
  - Digital images of exhibitions, 2005; 57 computer files (TIFF)
- Printed material documenting exhibits and events, 2002-2005; Accession 2006-A-201
  - Printed material documenting exhibits and events, 2002-2005 (Box 1)
- Booklet, "Selected Exhibitions: Yale School of Architecture Gallery 1998-2006", Accession 2006-A-217
  - Booklet, "Selected Exhibitions: Yale School of Architecture Gallery 1998-2006" (Box 1)
- Eero Saarinen symposium material, 2005; Accession 2006-A-261
  - Correspondence
    - McLaughlin, Donal, 2005 March 10 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Warnecke, John Carl, 2005 March 24 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Statement by Robert Venturi, 2005 April 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Photographs of Sarrinen meeting at Robert A.M. Stern Architects in New York, 2004 December 17; 11 (Box 3)
  - KDN Films, "Eero Saarinen: The Documentary,", computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, commercially-produced, optical disk (DVD) (Box 2U)
- "Eero Sarrinen and the David S. Ingalls Rink," exhibition curation and design pamphlet, 2003; Accession 2007-A-171
  - "Eero Sarrinen and the David S. Ingalls Rink," exhibition curation and design pamphlet, 2003 (Box 1)
- Digital images of exhibits [computer files], 2006-2007; Accession 2007-A-186 (Box 1–6)
  - "Prairie Skyscraper: Frank Lloyd Wright's Price Tower,", 2006 February 13 - May 5; 26 computer files (TIFF)
  - "Disclose" (Year End Exhibition of Student Work), 2006 May 19 - August 4; 52 computer files (TIFF)
  - "Team 10: A Utopia of the Present,", 2006 September 5 - October 20; 44 computer files (TIFF)
  - "Some Assembly Required: Contemporary Prefabricated Houses,", 2006 October 27 - 2007 February 2; 48 computer files (TIFF)
  - "UNStudio: Evolution of Space,", 2007 February 12 - May 4; 48 computer files (TIFF)
- "Spaces: The Architecture of Paul Rudolph" [videorecording], 1983; Accession 2007-A-232
  Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
  - "Spaces: The Architecture of Paul Rudolph," commercially-produced, 1983; videotape (VHS) (Box 1)
- Exhibitions [computer files], 2006-2008; Accession 2008-A-102 (Box 1)
  - 2006
    - Graduate Drawing Seminar: John Blood, Turner Brooks, Sophia Gruzdys, 2006 January 9 - March 3; 19 computer files (TIFF)
    - Takenaka Internship: Andrei Harwell; David Schwarz Internship and traveling Fellowship: Marisa Kurtzman; George Nelson Scholarship: Michelle Naomi Darling; Digital Media: John Eberhart, Faculty, 2006 March 18 - August 21; 54 computer files (TIFF)
    - Rome Project: Alexander Purves, Stephen Harby, Faculty, 2006 September 1 - October 27; 42 computer files (TIFF)
  - 2007
    - Graduate Drawing Seminars: Kent Bloomer, Phil Grausman, Ed Parker, William Butler, Sophia Gruzdyz, Dino Marcantonio, Paloma Pajares, Faculty, 2007 January 9 - March 3; 97 computer files (TIFF)
    - Tanenaka Internship: March Guberman; David Schwarz Internship and Traveling Fellowship: Geoffrey Lawson; George nelson Scholarship: Brook Denison; Digital Media: John Eberhart, Faculty, 2007 March 19 - May 30; 31 computer files (TIFF)
    - Well Done: Year End Exhibit of Student Work, 2007 May 18 - June 1; 23 computer files (TIFF, JPEG)
    - A Field Guide to Sprawl, 2007 August 30 - October 19; 15 computer files (TIFF)
    - Building Project: Adam Hopfner, Faculty; Building Systems Integration: Martin Finio, Faculty, 2007 October 29 - December 21; 24 computer files (TIFF)
  - 2007-2008
    - Ecology.Design.Synergy, 2007 October 29 - 2008 February 1; 14 computer files (TIFF)
- Exhibit and event materials, 2005-2008; Accession 2009-A-053
  - Powerpoint images from Marc Guberman for "On the Waterfront" symposium and Gehry Goldberger talk, 2006 March - April (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Exhibition post card "Ecology.Design.Synergy" Behnisch and Transsolar Climate Engineering, 2007 October 29 - 2008 February 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Exhibition post card "Building Connections", Center for Architecture, 2007 June 28 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Final Review poster, 2007 April-May (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Poster, Robert Stern -"Reminder dinner at the loft", 2008 January 24 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Exhibition post card "Painting the Glass House", 2008 February 11 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Constructs", 2008 Spring (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Exhibition post card "Well Done" end of year exhibit, 2007 May 18 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Brochures, 2008 May (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Mini poster Lectures, Symposia and Exhibitions, 2007 Fall (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Mini poster Lectures, Symposia and Exhibitions, 2008 Spring (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Exhibition postcard for Field Guide to Sprawl, 2007 August-October (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Postcard for Alumni Reception at the AIA Convention, 2008 May 4 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Postcard Yale Art and Architecture Building Stamp Dedicaton, 2005 August 31 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Symposium program "Mobile Anxieties, 2008 April 11 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Symposium program "Sustainable Architecture, Today and Tomorrow", 2008 April 4 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - International Contemporary Furniture Fair brochure -work of YSoA Massimo Scolari Advanced Studio, 2008 May 17-20 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dean's Council meeting, Columbus, Indiana and Cincinannti, Ohio, postcard, 2008 May 8-10 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Fan, 2008 May (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Yale Architecture Film Series poster, 2007 (Box 2)
  - Yale Architecture Film Series poster, 2008 (Box 2)
  - International Contemporary Furniture Fair press kit, 2008 May 17-20; 37; (30 JPG, 4 PDF, 2 TIF, 1 DOC); 19 computer files (JPEG, PDF, DOC, TIFF) (Box 3)
- "Model City: Buildings & Projects by Paul Rudolph for Yale and New Haven" [computer files], 2008; Accession 2009-A-189
  The materials consist of digital photographs documenting a three dimensional piece of concrete form work from the exhibit.
  - 01-002, computer file (TIFF)
  - 01-003, computer file (TIFF)
  - 01-004, computer file (TIFF)
  - 01-005, computer file (TIFF)
  - 01-006, computer file (TIFF)
  - 01-007, computer file (TIFF)
- School of Architecture exhibits, 2008-2009; Accession 2009-A-192; 2721.76 (Box 1–3)
  The materials are open for research.
  - A/Z: Year End Exhibition of Student Work 2007-2008, 2008 May 23 - August 22; 15; 15 computer files (TIFF)
  - Model City: Buildings and Projects by Paul Rudolph for Yale and New Haven, 2008 November 3 - 2009 February 15; 35; 35 computer files (TIFF)
  - Hawaiian Modern: The Architecture of Vladimir Ossipoff, 2009 August 28 - October 24; 25; 25 computer files (TIFF)
- Year-end student work exhibits [computer files], 2006-2009; Accession 2009-A-212; 10,957 megabytes (Box 1–3)
  - Year-End Exhibit of Student Work 2005-2006, 2006 May 22 - August 7
    - Advanced Graduate Section
      - Angel Beale; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Jamie Berg; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Bryan Berkas; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Rebecca Beyer; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Jack Brough; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Terrence Chew; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Cheng Hui Chua; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Christine Chow; Master of Architecture I
      - Robert Cole; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Daniel Colvard; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Cody Davis; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Pilip Drew; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Travis Eby; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Seher Erdogan; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Isidro Garcia; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Leslie Goedken; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Nicholas Hanna; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Reuben Herzl; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Parsa Khalili; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Jason Kim; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Isaiah King; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Eric Krancevic; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Louise Levi; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Joshua Lewandowski; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Patrick Lun; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Felicia Martin; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Alexander Maymind; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Patrick McGowan; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Marianna Mello; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Lauren Mishkind; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Kristin Mueller; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Shane Neufeld; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Mieko Okamoto; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Cheon-Kang Park; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Miriam Peterson; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Rachel Reese; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Karen Grace Rizvi; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Matthew Roman; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Roberto Rossi; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Tal Schori; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Zakery Snider; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Trisha Snyder; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Meghan Spigle; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Tom Tang; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Julianna Von Zumbusch; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Leah Rosa Weinberg; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Emily Wells; Master of Architecture I, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Shu Chang; Master of Architecture II, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Christine Chow; Master of Architecture II, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Marc Cucco; Master of Architecture II, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Mwangi Gathinji; Master of Architecture II, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Mark Gausepohl; Master of Architecture II, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Yijun Qian; Master of Architecture II, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Saifullah Sami; Master of Architecture II, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Daniel Yoder; Master of Architecture II, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Lucas Cohen; Master of Environmental Design, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Iben Falconer; Master of Environmental Design, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Olga Pantiledou; Master of Environmental Design, 2009; computer file (PDF)
    - H.I. Feldman Prize Section, 2009
      - Bryan Berkas, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Travis Eby + Seher Erdogan, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Seher Erdogan, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Isaiah King, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Parsa Khalili + Matthew Roman, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Jason Kim, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Isaiah King + Eliza Higgins, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Patrick Lun, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Lauren Mishkind, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Kristin Mueller + Yijun Qian, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Felix Raspall Galli, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Zakery Snider, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Tom Tang + Patrick McGowan, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Emily Wells -Feldman Prize Winner, 2009; computer file (PDF)
    - 1st& 2ndYear Student Work Section, 2009
      - 1stYear MED, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 501a Ben Pell, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 501a Brennan Buck, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 501a Jennifer Leung, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 501a Joyce Hsiang, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 501a Martin Cox, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 501a Sunil Bald, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 502ba Alan Organschi, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 502b Amy Lelyveld, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 502b Bimal Mendis, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 502b Joeb Moore, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 502b Peter deBretteville, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 503a Andrew Benner, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 503a Keith Krumwiede, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 503a Makram el Kadi, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 503a Mario Gooden, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 503a Martin Finio, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 503a Mimi Hoang, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 504b Alan Plattus, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 504b Andrea Kahn, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 504b Ben Pell, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 504b Makram el Kadi, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 504b Peggy Deamer, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 504b Tim Love, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 506b Building Project_Teams A+C, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 506b Building Project_Teams D+E, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 506b Building Project_Winning Team, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - 509a 1st Year Post-Pro, 2009; computer file (PDF)
    - Undergraduate Student Section, 2009
      - Michael Barry, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Erica Bergman, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Megan Enyeart, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Keir Evans, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Marcus Hooks, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Michael Huang, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Andrea Leung, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Marilynn Ly, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Nancy Nichols, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Cristian Oncescu, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Christopher Palencia, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Michael Pearce, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Adler Prioly, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Nathalie Razo, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Benjamin Sachs, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - William Sankey, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Troy Suttle, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Yasemine Tarhan, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - Garrett Wong, 2009; computer file (PDF)
      - William Wong, 2009; computer file (PDF)
  - Well Done: 2006-2007 Year-End Exhibit of Student Work, 2007 May 18 - June 1
    - Advanced Graduate Section
      - Joseph Alguire; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (INDD)
      - Sandra Arndt; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - E. Sean Bailey; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Elizabeth Barry; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Gabrielle Brainard; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Harris Ford; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Khai Fung; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (INDD)
      - Anya Grant; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Sallie Hambright; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Greg Heasley; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Sini Kamppari; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Serra Kiziltan; Master of Architecture I, computer file (AI), 2007
      - Clarisse Labro; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PSD)
      - Christopher Lee; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Steven Lee; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PSD)
      - Young Jin Lee; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PDF)
      - Heather Loeffler; Master of Architecture I, 2007; computer file (PDF)